Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
Run, Run!
Episode 4
This thing does not belong to our world
Did this thing come out of that rift?
Then we have to do some research to find out.
we need to find him
quick
Find Weslie quickly
To catch me, they mobilized all their troops like this
Is my wool so precious?
Gotta find that guy
It was he who ruined our Bulala
Go ahead
What ruined Bulala
I didn’t do it at all
Could it be them
If I hide like this, I will be caught sooner or later.
Gotta get out of here quickly
Children are not allowed to imitate
Do we really want this?
That’s right, let’s go soon
But I’m still scared
Didn’t you say that the guard at the side entrance was lax
and that is why you wanted to disguise yourself like this?
Don’t be afraid. Go
Okay
Sure enough, there’s no one watching over here.
Who is coming?
this
It turned out to be for delivering Bulala.
Yes, yes, I’m here to deliver Bulala
By the way, why do you have to stand guard here today?
Something happened in the palace
Be on guard
The vacation is all in vain
Thanks for your hard work
How could this happen?
Speaking of which, I’ve never seen you before.
You shouldn’t be
a fake soldier?
Discovered so quickly
I’m kidding
Who would be so bold as to pretend to be a soldier?
This is a serious crime
Yes, who would be so bold?
Then let me do a routine check.
It would be bad if it was found to be empty.
Come and help
The criminal who destroyed Bulala has been found
No more checking
We’re going to help
You go in quickly
It’s so dangerous. It scares me to death.
Finally came in
Aren’t you afraid at all?
this experience
I have experienced it dozens of times in my world.
How could I be afraid?
If only I could be as brave as you
you can do it
Right
Then where should we start looking?
He was caught as Bulala
It will definitely be put in the warehouse
Okay, let’s head to the warehouse
Be careful
This way, this way
You are really familiar with this place
arrive
That moving Bulala is so disgusting
Actually ruined our Bulala
If we catch him, we’ll definitely make him pay.
The moving Bulala
Are they talking about Weslie?
If your friend leaves, he can just leave
Why destroy Bulala?
Without Bulala we would be attacked by monsters
monster
don’t you know
Every full moon night
There will always be a monster coming
It won’t come until we pay enough Bulala
so serious
I believe Weslie wouldn’t do such a thing
Let’s find him and ask him clearly.
All right
Wolffy
are you too hot
Is there any way
It’s really too crowded
Then take a rest
Okay
Soldiers are coming. Hide quickly.
There are some here too
It’s too late to pick it up. Run back quickly
you
Did you find the prisoner there?
I didn’t
Fortunately, I hid quickly
Where did he go? Where?
too heavy
Who wants to work overtime to catch this prisoner?
I’m exhausted
Too bad
I can still stretch
Let’s go over there and have a look
Okay
It’s really awesome
I also just learned that my hands and feet can stretch
Why have my legs become shorter?
There’s movement over there
Teach you to show off!
Sorry, dear, I haven’t mastered the new skills yet.
Is it over there?
Go ahead
I hid so well and was discovered
Don’t run
No way
Where are the people?
The prisoner seems to have escaped back to the warehouse.
Go catch him quickly
Don’t run
Although I don’t know what happened
it’s finally safe
Doesn’t seem to be chasing
Who are you
Sp-
ar-
ky
Who are you
The person who ruined Bulala
I
Did you know that without Bulala the monster would come?
How many residents’ homes will be destroyed by then?
Misunderstanding, I’m not
No need to quibble, just take it easy
Turned
Have some ability
Then
Are you okay?
Someone come here
The man who destroyed Bulala was in the garden
believe it or not
But it’s true that I didn’t destroy Bulala.
I’ll prove it to you
what happened
Come and see everyone
The Bulala that everyone paid so hard
It was ruined by this foreigner named Weslie.
why did he do this
yes
I thought he was pretty good before.
Could it be a misunderstanding?
yes
It can’t be a misunderstanding
We two brothers watched him destroy it with our own eyes.
Then why don’t you stop it?
this
Now all the Bulala in the sky is collected
Where can we go to get more?
That’s right
But there’s no way
Tonight is the night of the full moon
If we don’t hand over Bulala
The monster is coming
Coming
It seems that we can only pay tribute to Bulala.
In order to pay Bulala
I took apart all the beds at home
How can we live like this in the future?
I don’t even know how to get enough Bulala
It’s all because of the person who ruined Bulala
No! Please, I beg you.
This is the doll my grandma made for me
Stop making trouble. Nothing is more important now than having enough Bulala.
If you want to blame it, just blame Weslie who ruined Bulala.
my doll
let’s go
Thank you big brother
You, you are the one who ruined Bulala
and made everyone become so
not done by me
not him
He said he didn’t do it
Don’t look at us
It doesn’t matter who it is anymore
Everyone’s problems are caused by the monster
Let me try to solve it
You?
That’s a monster that even the king can’t defeat.
That’s it
Stop trying to be a hero here
Someone catch him
Everyone, just wait.
Don’t run
So handsome
which side are you from
I hope you can do what you say
These are my latest drones developed
Let them explore the rifts on our behalf
and Looking for Weslie and Wolffy
You two must be okay
To be continued